[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the name of Doc Browns dog in the film Back to the Future?", "correct_answer": "Einstein", "incorrect_answers": ["Shep", "Edsel", "Shaggy"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these movies was not directed by Francois Truffaut?", "correct_answer": "Close Encounters of the Third Kind", "incorrect_answers": ["The Last Metro", "Day for Night", "Jules and Jim"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which character from the movie House of 1000 Corpses was made into Fish Boy?", "correct_answer": "Bill", "incorrect_answers": ["Brian", "Barry", "Bob"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these thermal emissions of light is the rarest in nature?", "correct_answer": "Blue thermal emission", "incorrect_answers": ["They are all equally frequent", "Red  thermal emission", "White thermal emission"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the name of Thailand before it was called Thailand?", "correct_answer": "Siam", "incorrect_answers": ["Singapore", "Macau", "Persia"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The highest concentration of vitamin C in animals bodies is in their liver. Which of these animals has the largest quantity of vitamin C in its liver?", "correct_answer": "Calf", "incorrect_answers": ["Pig", "Chicken", "None of these"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Slugs have how many tentacles on their head?", "correct_answer": "4", "incorrect_answers": ["8", "7", "3"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following people was a big fan of bowling?", "correct_answer": "Luther", "incorrect_answers": ["Mozart", "Cromwell", "Napolen"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "A teenage girl who is very thin and obsesses about losing weight may have an eating disorder.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "If you eat more protein, youll build more muscle.", "correct_answer": "Somewhat True", "incorrect_answers": ["True", "No Way", "False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Cables are essential for the transfer of data. The first cable to transfer instantaneous communications across the ocean was laid in this year.", "correct_answer": "1858", "incorrect_answers": ["1950", "1924", "1908"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who did David McCallum portray in the film The Great Escape?", "correct_answer": "Lt. Cmdr. Eric Ashley-Pitt, Dispersal", "incorrect_answers": ["Archibald Ives, the Mole", "Lt. MacDonald, Intelligence", "Lt. Cavendish, the Surveyor"]}]